Fishing industry suppresses it:
"Industrial disease."
Yeah, but it's just one man.
We don't even know what happened.
Just one man on video.
Not everyone has the foresight
to die in front of a camera.
The ones we don't see
worry me.
Fish is shipped
all over the world from there.
How many people read your paper
over a plate of sushi every day?
Alan, we have almost
no freelance budget anymore,
and after H1 ended up--
you wait...a few days,
this will be tweeted and YouTubed
all over the planet.
We don't want to be the paper
that cries wolf.
I'll show it to Hobart.
He does our health stuff now.
Are you going to give him
my story?
You're going to give him
my story, aren't you, Lorraine?
No, Alan, I'm trying
to help you.
It's just one man on a bus.
I taped this meeting.
We need more information
than that.
This story runs
in the Chronicle,
I will sue your ass!